[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the newspaper editor who carries out a campaign against Spider-Man?", "correct_answer": "J. Jonah Jameson", "incorrect_answers": ["Lou Grant", "Perry White", "Jonah Jameson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What bands music videos has Jackass director Jeff Tremaine also directed?", "correct_answer": "Turbonegro", "incorrect_answers": ["Disturbed", "Sister Sledge", "CKY"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the main protagonist of the Resident Evil movie trilogy?", "correct_answer": "Alice", "incorrect_answers": ["Merry", "Donna", "Carren"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the national motto of the Republic of Indonesia, Bhinneka Tunggal Ika?", "correct_answer": "Unity in Diversity", "incorrect_answers": ["Past Present Future", "Progress and Stability", "We Are Strong Together"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a type of spider?", "correct_answer": "Glass spider", "incorrect_answers": ["Trapdoor spider", "Brown recluse spider", "Bird-dropping spider"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The top grossing movie of 1985 was Back to the Future, trailed closely by two movies, starring this man.", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Cruise", "Eddie Murphy", "Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clark Wilhelm Griswold, Jr.", "correct_answer": "Vacation", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Mom", "The Great Outdoors", "Ferris Buellers Day Off"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the number of heavens in Islamic tradition. It is also the figurative number of seas.", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "3", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Four Emmys!  Four Grammys! Three Oscars! But most people know him best for his one Tony - the 1976\u2019s Tony for Best Musical Score for A Chorus Line. Who is this American composer?", "correct_answer": "Marvin Hamlisch", "incorrect_answers": ["Oscar Hammerstein III", "Cole Porter", "Oscar Hammerstein IV"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which President of the United States did Ben Stiller voice in the animated television series Libertys Kids?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "John Adams", "Abraham Lincoln"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do mathematicians call any rectangular table of numbers?", "correct_answer": "A matrix", "incorrect_answers": ["A  Latin square", "A polynomial", "A  factorial"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which continent is the famous active volcano Mount Nyiragongo located?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Australia", "South America"]}]